婚宴承办公司给了我十二道开胃菜单
So the caterer sent me this list of 12 appetizers,
我得选出六道
and I have to narrow it down to six.
食物问题  交给我吧
Food? Oh, give me.
莫妮卡跟你们提过我们的婚礼
So did Monica tell you about this great band called the Swing Kings
要请"摇摆国王"来演唱吗
that we're trying to get to play at the wedding?
你什么时候开始喜欢摇摆音乐了
Since when are you into swing music?
一直很喜欢  我以前会跑遍全城听乐队演出
Since forever! I used to go all over town listening to bands!
钱德勒
Chandler?
从GAP那支广告开始喜欢
Gap commercial.
-你打电话预定他们了吗  -我会打的
- Did you book them? Did you call? - I will.
要我打吗
Do you want me to call?
我打就行  你只需要做好你的工作
No, I'll do it. You just stick to your job.
-你的工作是什么  -别碍事
- What is your job? - Staying out of the way.
根本无法取舍  莫妮卡
This is impossible, Monica.
这十五道菜你都保留吧
Why don't you just pick all 15.
-只有十二道而己  -对  我加了三道
- There were only 12. - Oh, yeah, I added three.
什么是花生酱手指
What are peanut-butter fingers?
你好
Well, hello.
她好可爱
She's cute.
我们可以跟她搭讪吗
Should we go try to talk to her?
当然
Sure.
这是我订婚之后最大的收获之一
That's one of the great things about being engaged.
跟美女说话再也不会紧张了
I'm not nervous talking to pretty girls anymore.
你们能过来帮帮我吗
Could you guys help me?
我来帮你搬那个
Yeah, let me get that for you.
-很重的  -没问题
- It's really heavy. - I got it.
嗨  我是罗斯  他是我朋友钱德勒
So hi, I'm Ross, and this is my friend Chandler.
我是克丽丝汀
I'm Kristen.
克丽丝汀  嗨  你刚搬来吗
Kristen, hi. Are you new to the area?
如果你刚搬来  我可以带你四处参观一下
Because if you are, I'd love to show you around sometime.
其实我是从四条街外搬过来的
I actually just moved from four blocks over.
但这里简直像是另一个世界
But this block is like another world.
事实上  这个街区的历史确实非常有趣
Actually, it does have a very interesting history.
这条街是纽约第一条
This street is the first street in the city
有下水道系统的街道
to have an underground sewer system.
在那之前  污水跟粪便
Before that, sewage and waste...
会直接流到街上
...would just flow right down the street.
有时深及脚踝
Sometimes ankle-deep.
进展很顺利嘛
Smooth.
你说什么
Excuse me?
搬完家你一定会肚子饿
You're gonna be starving after all this moving.
想跟我一起去吃晚餐吗
What do you say I take you to dinner tonight?
-我很乐意  -太棒了
- I'd like that. - Great.
我帮你把箱子搬上去
Let me take this up for you.
-你先请  -不  你先请
- After you. - Oh, no. After you.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
是我搭错筋  还是搭对衣了
Am I crazy, or does this totally go?
我的天啊  你看起来好漂亮
Oh, my God! You look so beautiful!
谢谢你  瑞秋  可你快看莫妮卡啊
Thank you, Rachel. But look at Monica!
就是它了  就是这件
This is it. Yeah, this is the one.
真不敢相信我竟然找到了
I can't believe I found it.
你看起来好漂亮
Wow, you look so beautiful.
我要是认识你  一定被你感动哭了
If I knew you, I'd cry.
我是莫妮卡·盖勒  想哭就哭吧
I'm Monica Geller. Ball like a baby.
我是梅根·巴利
I'm Megan Bailey.
你找到合适的婚纱了吗
Have you found your dress yet?
这些婚纱都很漂亮...
No, these dresses are all so amazing...
但我买不起
but there's no way I could afford one.
我也是
No, I can't offord this either.
我只是来这里挑款式的
I'm here to figure out which one I want,
然后我会到克莱门婚纱店买
then I'll get it at Kleinmars, this discount place in Brooklyn,
他们后天要搞大减价
day after tomorrow they are having a huge sale.
-多谢提醒  -你什么时候结婚
- Thanks for the tip. - When are you getting married?
我没准备结婚  我只是想试穿婚纱
I'm not. I just like to try these on.
我也喜欢试穿
I do the same thing.
我开玩笑的  我的婚期是7月25日
I'm just kidding. I'm getting married July 25.
我也是在开玩笑
I'm just kidding too.
我十二月结婚
I'm getting married in December.
-你什么时候结婚  -5月15日
- When are you getting married? - May 15.
近在眼前了  你请的哪位摄影师
It's getting close. Who's your photographer?
-杰佛瑞  -我们跟他谈过
- Jeffrey. - We met with him.
他拿裸体婚纱照给你们看了吗
Did he show you the photos of the nude wedding he did?
那个伴郎吗  哇
The best man? Wow!
我知道  我差点为他取消了婚礼
I know. I almost called off my wedding.
你请了哪个乐队
Who's your band?
我未婚夫想请摇摆国王
My fiance wants The Swing Kings.
你真幸运  我未婚夫想请重金属乐队"尸体"
You're lucky. My fiance wants the heavy metal band, Carcass.
是尸体  还是湿体
Is that spelled with a C or a K?
天啊  根本无所谓  他们都很赞
Oh, my god. It doesn't matter, they're both great!
听我一句劝  别在这里买婚纱
Oh, you know what? You know what? Don't buy that here.
在这里挑好样式  然后到克莱门婚纱店买
Now that you know what you want you should go to Kleinman's
这里的婚纱太贵了
and get it half off. This place is so overpriced.
我是这里的老板
I own this store.
这件婚纱有别的颜色吗  还是...
So does this come in another color, or...?
嗨  你要搬进来还是搬走
Hi. You moving in or moving out?
-搬进来  -需要我帮忙吗
- Moving in. - Can I give you a hand?
好吧  但你得小心点
Okay, but be careful.
之前帮我搬东西的家伙背部拉伤先撤了
Guy who was helping me had to leave because he hurt his back.
-是你男朋友吗  -不是
- Boyfriend? - No.
我是乔伊
I'm Joey.
我是克丽丝汀
Kristen.
你的名字真好听
What a beautiful name.
你叫什么来着
What is it again?
克丽丝汀
Kristen.
-你住在附近吗  -我就住在那边
- You live around here? - Right down there.
我得给你提个醒
Let me give you a little tip.
别在那个门廊上睡觉
Don't take a nap on this stoop,
醒来之后  你的鞋子可能会被偷
or you could wake up with your shoes gone.
-我会记住的  -好
- I'll remember that. - Okay.
你今晚愿意跟我一起吃饭吗
Listen, would you like to have dinner with me tonight?
我今晚有约了  明天可以吗
I have plans tonight. How about tomorrow?
可以啊  这个要搬到哪里
Sounds great. Well, where does this go?
你看起来很壮  这个交给我
You look strong. Why don't I take that,
-你去帮我搬箱子吧  -好
- and you grab one of the boxes. - Okay, yeah.
我还是搬这个吧
Yeah, I'll get this one.
这里就是布鲁克林
So this is Brooklyn?
听着  通常每件婚纱一个尺寸只有一件
Listen up. There's usually only one dress in each size.
他们一开门  分散行动
So when they open those doors, fan out.
这就是你们的目标  记住款式
This is what you're looking for. Memorize it.
找到这件婚纱后就吹哨子  好吗
When you locate the dress, blow on these, all right?
用力吹三声  听到哨音后马上集合
Three sharp blasts. When you hear it, come running.
他来了
Here he comes!
-他们在推我  -别那么孩子气
- They're pushing! - Don't be a baby!
-别挡路  -冲吧
- Out of the way! - Let's go!
瑞秋  快点
Rachel?! Come on!
不是这件  不是这件
No, not it. Not it. Not it.
别推我
Don't crowd me.
就是它  就是这件婚纱  太完美了
This is it! This is the dress! It's perfect!
对不起  这件是我的
I'm sorry, this one's taken!
-梅根  -莫妮卡
- Megan! - Monica!
-你来了  -是啊
- You came! - Yeah!
-这是我的婚纱  -不
- This is my dress! - No!
没错  就是我的  你见我试穿过
Yes it is. You saw me wearing it.
而现在你会见我把它买回家
And now you'll see me buying it.
你这个疯婆子
You freak!
如果不是我  你根本不知道这个地方
You wouldn't even have known about this place if it wasn't for me!
跟我打架  你会吃亏的
Look, you don't want to fight me.
那可难说  我很彪悍的
Maybe I do. I'm pretty feisty!
我来了  我来了
I'm coming! I'm coming!
好吧
Okay!
我该往哪儿跑
Hey? Oh, what do I do?!
你在做什么  你找到婚纱了吗
What are you doing? Did you find the dress?
你找到婚纱了吗
Did you find the dress?
没有  快救我出去
No! You gotta get me out of here Phoebe!
这些血拼的女人都疯了
These bargain shoppers are crazy!
-我们得去找莫妮卡  -你得抓住我的手
- We've gotta get Monica. - You gotta hold my hand!
天啊
Oh, my god.
借过  借过
Excuse me! Excuse me!
快跑  快跑
Go! Go! Go!
快跑
Go!
罗斯  你那天跟她约会还顺利吧
So, Ross, how was your date the other night?
你跟她提过只要一按马桶
Did you tell her about the magical ride
魔法之旅就启程了吗
that starts with the flush of every toilet?
尽管笑吧
Laugh all you want,
她给我留言说  还想再跟我约会
but she actually left me a message saying she'd like to go out again.
我正要打电话给她
In fact, I'll go call her right now.
我一定会转告她  我朋友钱德勒说...
And I'll make sure and tell her my friend Chandler says...
钱德勒
Chandler.
抱歉昨晚我失约了  我有个约会
Sorry I didn't stop by last night, but I had a date.
你说你凌晨一点要过来
Joe, when it's 1:00 in the morning
就算你放我鸽子也没有关系
and you don't come by, that's okay.
我去跟一个辣妹约会了
It was with this really hot girl
她刚刚搬到对街
who just moved in right across the street.
-真的吗  她住在对街  -对
- Really? Right across the street? - Yeah.
-你什么时候认识她的  -两天前
- When did you meet her? - Two days ago.
太棒了
Excellent!
罗斯也认识了一个姑娘
You know, Ross met somebody too.
怎么样
How'd it go?
很好  我们星期六要再出去玩
Great. We're going out again Saturday.
但我刚刚发现她也在跟别人约会
But I just found out she's also seeing some other guy.
真的吗
Really?
乔伊  如果你是罗斯  你会怎么做
Joe, what would you do if you were in Ross' situation?
我跟他情况差不多
I sort of am.
跟我约会的姑娘也在跟别人约会
I'm dating this girl who's also seeing another guy.
但我一点都不担心
But I'm not worried about it.
你不必担心
You shouldn't be.
我可不想当你的竞争者
Believe me, I wouldn't want to be the guy who's up against you.
那个蠢蛋一定会输给你的
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
这真的太有意思了
So this is nice.
真希望我能留下来  相信我
I wish I didn't have to go. Believe me.
但可惜我得走了
But unfortunately I have to.
对了  跟你们约会的姑娘叫什么名字
By the way, what's the name of the girl you're dating?
-克丽丝汀·莱夫  -再见
- Kristen Leigh. - Bye.
很明显  我们之中只有一个人
Well, obviously only one of us
可以继续跟她约会
can keep dating her.
没错  我们该怎么决定
Obviously. So how do we decide?
好了  我们得客观地来解决这件事
Well, now, let's look at this objectively.
我觉得我该跟她约会
I think I should date her.
或是我该跟她约会
Or I'm the one who dates her.
真有意思  但听好了 我跟她约会
That's interesting. But check this out. I date her.
好吧  但换个角度来说...
Yeah, I like that but just to go in another direction...
好吧  我们是讨论不出结果的
Okay. This can go on for a while.
-那么我们该点些吃的  -不  乔伊
- We should order some food, then. - No, Joey.
我们何不让她来决定
Look, why don't we just let her decide, okay?
我们都再跟她约会一次
We'll each go out with her one more time.
看看她比较喜欢谁
And we'll see who she likes best.
听起来很公平
That sounds fair.
我可能会带她到新开的法国餐厅吃饭
Maybe I'll take her to that new French restaurant down the street.
等一下  我们得对约会费用设下限制
Wait a second. We have to set a spending limit on the date.
我没钱带她到高级餐厅吃饭
I don't have the money to take her to a fancy place like that.
抱歉  那就是我的约会方式
Well, sorry. That's what I do on dates.
看来我得用我的约会方式了
Well, I guess I'll just have to do what I do on dates.
-我们来决定费用上限  -好吧
- So let's decide on a spending limit. - Yeah.
一片...
And a slice...
六块钱
...$6?
-我想说一百块  -好吧
- I was thinking more like 100. - Okay.
你能借我九十四块吗
Can I borrow $94?
我懂  你能帮我拿张面纸吗
I know. Can you hand me a tissue?
你家没有健怡可乐了
You're out of Diet Coke.
喂
Hello?
什么  你说什么
What? You what?
你给我听好了  小姐
You listen here, missy!
怎么了
What?
是梅根打来的
That was that girl Megan.
她预定了摇摆国王在我们婚礼那天演出
She booked The Swing Kings on the day of our wedding...
还说如果我不把婚纱让给她  就别想要回乐队
...and said I couldn't have them back unless I gave her the dress!
那么说可以请尸体了
Does that mean Carcass is available?
我该怎么办  我好喜欢那件婚纱
What am I gonna do? That's the dress! That is the dress!
钱德勒喜欢那个乐队  我该怎么办
Chandler wants the band. What do I do?
-想办法说服他放弃  -怎么说服
- Figure out a way to talk him out of it. - How?
你家的卫生纸用完了
You're out of toilet paper!
什么事
What's up?
我要来祝你约会顺利
I wanted to wish you good luck on your date.
-谢谢  -你们约几点
- Thanks. - What time are you meeting?
我们在葛兰梅西毕斯多餐厅订了八点的位子
We have 8:00 reservations at Grand Merci Bistro.
只剩下二十分钟  你最好快去换衣服
That's in 20 minutes. You'd better get dressed.
-我已经换好衣服了  -太好了
- I am dressed. - Oh, well, good.
对我来说
For me.
这是什么  你在敷脸
What's this? Did you give yourself a facial?
我的T字区经常出油
I have an oily T-zone.
好吧  兄弟
Okay, dude.
-你送了花给克丽丝汀  -没错
- You sent Kristen flowers? - That's right.
你花了一百块  你把钱花光了  你完蛋了
You spent $ 100. That's the limit. You're screwed!
我是在约会前送她花
Actually, I sent the flowers before the actual date,
所以严格来说
so technically, technically...
我没有犯规
...I didn't break any rules.
谢谢你顺路过来
Thanks for stopping by, though.
你真要那么玩吗  我也可以犯规
That's the way it's gonna be? I can break the rules too.
-你打算怎么办  -我不知道
- What are you gonna do? - I don't know.
为什么我一点都不惊讶
Why am I not surprised?
罗斯  我不会放过你的
Ross, I'm not gonna let you get away with this.
-你拿我没什么办法  -我们走着瞧
- I don't think you have much choice. - We'll see!
-再见  -再见
- Bye bye! - Bye bye.
只要薄薄地敷一层就好
Hey! So, just a light layer?
对  只要敷这里跟这里
Yeah, just here and there.
乔伊又把肉酱滴在栏杆上了
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
摇摆音乐太落伍了
Swing music is so out.
菲比  他得在这个房间里才听得到
Phoebe, he's gotta be in the room for that to work.
你们到底在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
我们在谈摇摆国王...
We're talking about The Swing Kings...
讨论到底该不该请他们来
...and wondering whether they're the right way to go.
有一次我去参加婚礼  请的就是摇摆乐队
I went to a wedding once where they had swing music...
两个月后他们就离婚了
...and two months later, the couple divorced.
我没说这其中有什么必然的联系
I'm not saying there's any connection here...
但他们告诉我就是为了乐队离的婚
...but they did tell me that's why they got divorced.
但我喜欢摇摆音乐
But I love swing music!
可摇摆国王实在不敢恭维
But The Swing Kings?
他们烂到有人听他们的演唱都会送命
They suck so much that people actually die at their concerts.
他们就是活不下去了
They just stop living.
可是莫妮卡跟我去听他们演唱会非常开心
All I know is that when Monica and I went to see them, we had fun.
其实还有一个原因
And there's another reason too.
-什么原因  -我不想说
- Well, what is the other reason? - I don't want to say.
你非说不可  或许这个理由很蠢
Well, you have to because maybe it's stupid.
莫妮卡跟我随着他们的音乐起舞...
It's just, while Monica and I were dancing to them...
那是我第一次知道...
...it was the first time I knew that...
你就是我想一辈子共舞的女人
...you were the woman that I wanted to dance all my dances with.
烂理由
Oh, crap.
-我们的桌子马上就准备好  -太棒了
- They said our table will be ready in a few minutes. - Oh, great.
-你的背好一点了吗  -没事了
- Is your back feeling better? - Yeah, that's fine.
我猜肌肉越多...
I guess the more muscles you have...
就越容易抽筋
...the more they can spasm out of control.
-克丽丝汀  -乔伊
- Kristen? - Joey!
-你来这里做什么  -我喜欢这家餐厅
- What are you doing here? - I like this place.
严格来说  我没有犯规  所以...
And technically, I'm not breaking any rules, so...
罗斯  他是乔伊  乔伊  罗斯
Well, Ross, this is Joey. Joey, Ross.
幸会
It's nice to meet you.
我以前有个朋友也叫乔伊
I used to have a friend named Joey.
但我现在跟他绝交了
I don't anymore.
我们的桌子马上就会准备好
Our table will be ready in a couple minutes.
好  我愿意跟你们一起等  谢谢
Sure, I would love to wait with you guys! Thanks!
乔伊  你看起来好眼熟
So, Joey, you look familiar.
你上过电视吗
Are you on TV or something?
乔伊不喜欢提这件事...
Joey doesn't like to talk about it...
但他主演过《我们的日子》
...but he's one of the stars of Days of Our Lives.
没错  你是演了个女人吗
That's right. Don't you play a woman?
一个被困在男人身体里的女人
A woman in a man's body.
这下好多了
Much better.
罗斯  真巧  我也觉得你很眼熟
So, you know Ross, it's funny, because you look familiar to me too.
你结过婚吗
Have you ever been married?
我结过婚  事实上  前几天...
Yes, I have. In fact, just the other day...
克丽丝汀跟我还谈到我结婚的事
...Kris and I were talking about how I've been married
还有我儿子
and how I have a son.
-小艾力克  -没错
- Yeah, little Eric. - That's right.
等一下  不  是班才对
Wait. No, Ben.
你只结过一次婚吗
So you've just been married the one time, then?
-这个嘛  -你结过两次婚
- Well... - You've been married twice?
对  那个...
Yes. And...
之后又结了一次
...another time after that.
天啊  我饿了
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
乔伊  你曾经在约会时饿到...
Joey, have you ever been so hungry on a date...
趁女伴去上洗手间偷吃掉她的食物吗
...that when the girl goes to the bathroom, you eat some of her food?
你说是服务生吃掉了我的蟹饼
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
罗斯  你的第一段婚姻为什么会失败
So, Ross, now why did that first marriage break up?
因为你前妻是异性恋  还是因为她是同性恋
Was it because the woman was straight or because she was a lesbian?
-你们认识吗  -不认识
- Do you two know each other? - No.
只是罗斯看起来像是那种
Just seems like Ross is the kind of guy
结婚之后能把半直不弯的女人
who'd marry a woman on the verge of being a lesbian
彻底掰弯的男人
and then push her over the edge.
等一下  你拍过性病海报吧
Wait a minute! Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
你跟猴子同床共枕过吧
Have you ever slept in the same bed with a monkey?
别把马修扯进来
You leave Marcel out of this!
好吧  你曾经被自己的皮裤卡住过吧
Fine! You ever gotten stuck in a pair of your own leather pants?
你曾经把自己锁在电视柜里过吧   梅毒小子
Have you ever locked yourself in a TV cabinet, VD-boy?
猴子迷
Monkey-lover!
你觉得她是什么时候走的
Where do you think we lost her?
可能是说到性病那一段吧
Probably around gonorrhea.
-亲爱的  我回来了  -别进来
- Hi, honey, I'm home! - Don't come in here!
怎么了  你的另一个男朋友在里面吗
Why, do you have another boyfriend in there or something?
不  我们只会在他家胡搞
No. We only mess around at his place.
虽然是我开的头  但我开始心慌了
It's funny that I started it, but now it's scaring me,
你能出来吗
so could you come out here, please?
不行  我正穿着婚纱
No, I'm wearing a wedding dress.
你买到婚纱了  太棒了
You got a wedding dress? That's great.
对  但我要退回去
Yeah, but I'm not keeping it.
那我为什么不能看
Then why can't I see it?
应该可以
Oh. I guess you can.
但我得退回去  所以你绝对不能喜欢
But I have to return it, so you can't like it.
好吧  我发誓我会很讨厌
Okay, I promise. I'll hate it.
哇  你看起来好丑啊
Wow. You look hideous.
真的吗
Really?
那是我见过最丑的婚纱
Yeah. That's like the most ugliest dress I've ever seen.
你为什么要退回去
Why do you have to return it?
因为很不合身
Because it doesn't really fit.
还有  我订了摇摆国王
Oh, by the way, I booked The Swing Kings.
太棒了  谢谢
Oh, that's great. Thanks.
但那件婚纱  简直丑爆了
But that dress... I mean it's like... It's terrible.
-我想把它从你身上扯下来  -好吧
- It makes me want to rip it off you. - Okay.
但你不可以弄破
But you can't rip it.
弄破一点也没关系
Well, maybe a little.
你们想看看婚礼上的歌曲清单吗
Guys, you want to look at the song list for the wedding?
伙计们
Guys?
我还以为你会出去一整天
I thought you were gonna be gone all day.
好吧  发生了什么事
All right, what's going on?
对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我应该让你们这些小女生独处一下
I should probably leave you girls alone.
尽管笑吧  但十分钟后
Laugh all you want, but in 10 minutes,
我们的皮肤会变得又白又嫩
we'll have younger-looking skin.
她也该敷一下脸
You know, she could use a little...
好球  太帅了
Oh, nice shot! Yeah!